Your Excellency, bad news.
سعادتكم ، أخبار سيئة.
Young master and that merman got into a fight.
السيد الشاب وهذا الحوري دخل في معركة.
You don't have to worry about my family matters.
لا داعي للقلق بشأن شؤون عائلتي.
So that you won't accidentally hurt Senior Brother.
حتى لا تؤذي الأخ الأكبر عن طريق الخطأ.
Tomorrow is the day of Master's sacrifice.
غدا هو يوم تضحية السيد.
I'll wait for you at the usual place.
سأنتظرك في المكان المعتاد.
Stop!
قف!
Sis,
الاخت ،
who allowed you to enter my room?
من سمح لك بدخول غرفتي؟
I haven't asked you yet. Why are you asking about me?
أنا لم أسألك بعد.  لماذا تسأل عني؟
When did you
متى فعلت
raise such a pretty boy in the mansion,
تربية مثل هذا الفتى الجميل في القصر ،
Does Danmo know?
هل يعرف Danmo؟
You're doomed.
أنت محكوم.
What does it have to do with you who I raise?
ما علاقة بك من أقوم بتربيته؟
What does it have to do with Grand Tutor?
ما علاقة ذلك بـ Grand Tutor؟
Lin Weixu, let me tell you,
لين ويكسو ، دعني أخبرك ،
I only admit that Danmo is my future brother-in-law.
أنا أعترف فقط أن دانمو هو زوج أختي المستقبلي.
As for this stinky salted fish, don't even think about it.
أما بالنسبة لهذه السمكة المملحة ذات الرائحة الكريهة ، فلا تفكر في الأمر.
No way.
مستحيل.
Get him out of here.
اخرجه من هنا.
Execute.
ينفذ.
Ah,
آه،
Sis,
الاخت ،
it's not that serious, is it?
ليس الأمر بهذه الخطورة ، أليس كذلك؟
No,
لا،
you're going to kill me just for a little salted fish.
ستقتلني فقط من أجل سمكة مملحة صغيرة.
Are you my sister or not?
هل انت اختي ام لا
Does Danmo know?
هل يعرف Danmo؟
Lin Weixu,
لين ويكسو ،
you're in trouble.
انت في ورطة.
You stinky seafood. I'll kill you.
أنت المأكولات البحرية نتن.  سأقتلك.
I was trying to scare him.
كنت أحاول إخافته.
Where are your fins?
أين زعانفك؟
Mermen live in the sea with their fins,
تعيش حوريات البحر بزعانفها ،
no one would expose such an important thing
لن يفضح أحد مثل هذا الشيء المهم
to the outside.
إلى الخارج.
If you lose your fins,
إذا فقدت زعانفك ،
you'll be unable to move.
لن تتمكن من التحرك.
Until death.
حتى الموت.
But you're so good at kung fu,
لكنك جيد جدًا في الكونغ فو ،
I don't think you'll die so easily.
لا أعتقد أنك ستموت بسهولة.
It's because your brother is too weak.
هذا لأن أخيك ضعيف للغاية.
He has a strong tone,
لديه نبرة قوية ،
My little brother is a jerk,
أخي الصغير أحمق ،
but he's good at it.
لكنه جيد في ذلك.
That means
هذا يعني
those people are no match for you.
هؤلاء الناس ليسوا مثيل لك.
Why didn't you fight back?
لماذا لم تقاوم؟
Since you don't want to say it,
بما أنك لا تريد أن تقول ذلك ،
forget it. You should rest well in the mansion these days.
انسى ذلك.  يجب أن ترتاح جيدًا في القصر هذه الأيام.
Why are you so nice to me?
لماذا انت لطيف جدا معي؟
I told you,
أخبرتك،
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
That's how much
هذا كم
you like it.
هل أحببت ذلك.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Cold,
بارد،
It's so cold.
إنه بارد جدا.
Water Forbidden Curse.
لعنة الماء المحرمة.
Only the blood of my clan can relieve it.
فقط دماء عشيرتي يمكنها أن تريحها.